Reproductive Rights National Network Records, 1970-1985
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES IV. SUBJECT FILES
  - Birth control
    - Depo-Provera
      - General 1976-83, undated (Box 10, Folder 17-18)
      - Women's Reproductive Rights Information Centre, London: information packet 1984 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - International 1980-82 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - The Pill 1981-82, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Birth defects 1982-83, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Cartoons 1973-83, undated (Box 10, Folder 23-24)
  - Child abuse and incest 1981-82, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Childcare
    - General 1982-83, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - "A Parent's Guide to Day Care," U.S. Department of Health and Human Services Mar 1980 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - "Strategies to Address the Impact of the Economic Recovery Tax Act of 1981," Zeitlin and Campbell, National Women's Law Center, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Child custody and support 1981-82, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Civil rights 1980-84, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Constitutional Convention 1977-82, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Covert Action and Freedom of Information Act (FOIA)
    - General 1977-83, undated (Box 11, Folder 5-6)
    - Center for Constitutional Rights: reports (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Fund for Open Information and Accountability (FOIA), Inc.
      - General 1980-83, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Our Right to Know Apr 1981-Spring 1983 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - "Project Team Report for the Heritage Foundation" Nov 1980 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Democrats and gender gap 1981-83, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - DES (Diethylstilbestrol) 1980-81 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Disability
    - General 1980-84, undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Infants, "Baby Doe" 1982-84 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Economics/"Reaganomics"
    - General 1981-83, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Coalition on Women and the Budget 1983 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Health care costs 1980-82 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Employment
    - General 1980-83 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Discrimination
      - General 1980-84, undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - Amici on EEOC v. Olin 1981 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Wage gap 1980-84 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Unions and women 1981-83, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Women workers in the textile industry 1979-83 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Equal Rights Amendment
    - General 1977-84, undated (Box 12, Folder 5-6)
    - Anti-ERA materials undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - National Organization for Women pamphlets and flyers 1982-83, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - The Family 1978-84, undated (Box 12, Folder 9-10)
  - Family planning clinics 1981-84, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Feminism and the Women's Movement
    - General 1980-84, undated (Box 12, Folder 12-13)
    - International 1981-83, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Peace movement 1981-84, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Race 1981-83 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Feminist Self-Help Health Centers/Clinics 1979-81, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Fetal technology 1981-84, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Films and slideshows undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Health care 1981-83, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Health hazards 1981-84, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Infant formula 1981-84, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Infant mortality 1982-84, undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Infants, children, and teenagers 1980-83 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Lesbian rights
    - 1978-81 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - 1981-83, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Men and reproductive rights 1980-83, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Midwifery and home births 1980-83, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - "The New Right"
    - General 1977-84, undated (Box 13, Folder 4-8)
    - Creationism 1980-82, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Planned Parenthood New York City: packet and pamphlets 1980, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Politics
    - Electoral information 1979-85, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - 1980 Elections, Presidential and local (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - 1984 Election and Reagan administration (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Women 1980-83, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Population control 1977-82, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Pornography 1981-82, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Poverty 1980-83, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Pregnancy
    - General 1980-84, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - After 30, 1980-82, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Artificial insemination and surrogacy 1980-83, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Drug dangers 1973-84, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Racial discrimination 1981-84, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Religion and politics
    - General 1980-81, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Branch Davidian Seventh Day Adventist 1980-81, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Catholicism and women's issues 1979-83, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Judaism and reproductive rights 1980-82, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Protestantism 1978-82 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Secular humanism 1980-82 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Republican Party 1980-82 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Reproductive rights in the workplace 1981-82, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Rural women 1981-84 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Sexism and homophobia 1981-84 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Sexual discrimination and Title IX 1981-84 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Sexual harassment 1980-83, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Sexually transmitted infections 1980-82 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Solidarity 1983-84 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Sterilization
    - General 1973-83, undated (Box 14, Folder 20-22)
    - Congressional Record and Federal Register excerpts 1978, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Comments on U.S. Department of Health and Human Services sterilization regulations 1981-82 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation 1982-83 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - "Health Research Group Report Number 4 on Sterilization Abuse of the Nation's Poor Under Medicaid and Other Federal Programs" by Daniel W. Sigelman undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Students 1981-82 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Teenage sexuality and pregnancy
    - General 1979-84, undated (Box 15, Folder 6-7)
    - Brooklyn Teen Pregnancy Network 1983 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Parental notification
      - General 1980-83, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - N.Y. v. Heckler Brief and Appendix of Amici curiae 1983 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - "Teenage Pregnancy: The Problem That Hasn't Gone Away," Alan Guttmacher Institute 1981 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Third World women and health 1984 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Women in prison 1981-84 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Women's health 1973-84, undated (Box 15, Folder 14-15)
  - Workplace health hazards
    - General 1980-83, undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Global 1978-82, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Reproductive
      - General 1979-82, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - "Occupational Hazards to Reproduction: an annotated bibliography" by Wendy Chavkin with Laurie Welch 1980 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- SERIES V. ARTIFACTS
  - Stickers, button, and rubber stamps (Box 16)
- SERIES OV. OVERSIZE MATERIALS
  - Posters, periodicals, and miscellaneous (Box 17)